

# JAKOB KRISTENSEN

Moodys - Product consultant

## About me

27 years old computer scientist (Master in IT-Product development) with a focus on developing products and solutions targeted at the customer. I am looking for a highly social and innovative environment with focus on product development and optimization. A project is only complete when the customer is satisfied with the solution.

- "Create missionaries not mercenaries"

#### Contact me

- Ørestads boulevard 62, 3 t.v., Copenhagn S, 2300, Denmark
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakob-kristensen-409598141/

+4553619326

# Personal info

## Birthday

July 25th, 1995

Language Danish , Native English, Fluent German, Novice

# Education

Studying IT-Product development has taught me how to design and develop products and solution in close collaboration with the end-user and stakeholders. Through my projects and courses I have acquired skills within software development, interaction design, physical design, user research and prototyping. I have primarily dealt with concept- and software development, where I often have had the pleasure to evaluate and test with different user groups.

## **Master in IT-Product development**

Aarhus university (MSc)(2018 - 2020)

Featured courses: Innovation project, Entrepenuership, Shape-changing interfaces, Multimodal interaction etc.

#### **Bachelor in IT-Product development**

Aarhus university (BSc)(2015 - 2018)

Featured courses: Experimental System Development, Interaction design, Software Design & Software Architecture, Visualization & Project Communication etc.

#### **HTX** student exam

H.C. Ørsted gymnasium (2012 - 2015)

Mathematics and IT

## Experience

#### Product consultant

Moodys/BvD, Copenhagen, Denmark (2021.07.19 - )

Currently I am working as a **product consultant for Moodys**. As a product consultant I am responsible for new **integrations**, support of current solutions and new configurations for clients all over **Europe**. I help our clients to get the best possible integration, by **optimizing** their current compliance, credit and procurement process through **automation**, **data visibility** and notification flows.

## Case consultant

Kanpla, Aarhus C, Denmark (2021 - 2021.07.01)

Before the summer of 2021 I was working with the company **Kanpla** in order to help them bring their **software solution** to a **new market**. Kanpla is a newly found startup company. Their vision is to help bringing cafeterias into the digital age. My task is to **research** new markets for them to enter, come up with **solutions** and make sure that the it fits both the customers and the workers of the cafeteria.

#### Web scraper

IntelliJ IDEA

Arduino

Unity

Boligportal, Aarhus N, Denmark (2018 - 2020)

I worked part time at **Boligportal** as a **web scraper** in a team of 2 - 4. It was my job to **optimize** and **automize** manual data extraction tasks through **Python**, **RESTful API** and **JavaScript** in order to make sure that the rental site was always updated so the users would not miss newly announced apartments nor the customers had to wait for opening hours to get their products online. During my time, I helped Boligportal moving into **new markets** (**Sweden** and **Norway**) and migrate the department in Copenhagen with ours in Aarhus.

#### Skills and interests

Programming	Process-work	Product design
Python	Design-Thinking	Sketching
JavaScript(HTML, CSS)	Agile development	Visualization
C#	User research	Prototyping
SQL	Concept development	Physical design
IDEs	3D modelling	Interests

Autodesk Maya

**Autodesk Fusion** 

Rhino

ΔI

Data

Automation